Opening Talk
Today's talk is with Miki Fujisaki.
Today, I participated in the voice actor audition for Solotiv!
And I'm done!
I'm very happy to announce that I've finished the audition, and I've won the first place in the final!
I will be playing the lead role in my favorite manga King Al in the Light!
Thank you, I worked hard on my role model.
Miki, did you get some of your friends to help you out with your performance?
How did you do? Join me.
Those who played through my delivery.
Monomin is eating some kind of red bean paste.
So peaceful!
Miki thought of that!
It was just a fun delivery!
Lastly, Fu-chan helped me to deliver
together with Fu-chan!
Last day at noon
Miki started to cry while I was taking a glance.
It was the beginning of the delivery that was full of great memories for me too.
I was so happy to be able to do it with Miki on the last day.
Thank you so much.
Thanks to all of you who took the time to join us.
I thank you very much.
Thank you.
So the opening talk is over... Correction operation!
Correction operation!
Yes, yes, yes.
My glasses.
I changed my glasses already.
It's not that exciting, is it?
It's a summer dress.It's a summer outfit.
Yeah, I've been seeing a lot of summer outfits on Twitter.
Oh, you look adorable.
All Night Fujiko Reflections!
You've only had one review session.
There's a reflection meeting.
I had to do this first.
All Night Fujiko last Friday. The show Sakuma-san is on.
The elder sister group.
Saito, Yoshimura, and Hibi Takanashi were on the show.
We saw it too.
Did you see it?
It's a very egregious show.
It's like a real war zone.
What about the sexy actresses who used to be on the show?
How was it?
Well, frankly, I don't know.
That's why I came to say hello before I left.
Saito and Yoshimura came.
He said it would be better if I only put my arms around his shoulders.
That's true.
It's a show where most people can't play an active role.
I said, "I'm sorry.
I didn't think he'd go for such a big game.
Is that the last one?
I'd like to ask those of you who think you're the last one to stand up for a moment and say, "I'm in the big game.
I was in the big game.
That's right.
The three of you who won the big game.
They're all lined up.
They're miming.Imitation.
And those Fujiiko kids.
They told me two days ago.
Fifteen in a row.
Most of them are not that good.
We were supposed to do detailed impersonations.
Saito and Hibi said they could do it.
They said they could do the impersonations.
I was like, "I can do that," but "Takanashi can do the big slash.
It made me shiver.
That made me shiver the most.
Why did Takanashi say, "Let's do it with four people"?
Actually...
What happened to your voice?
I'm miming.
I really wanted to be a part of it.
But with my voice, I'm not sure I'd be able to make it to the world.
I see.
So I said I could do the imitation, and the three of us did it
During a commercial break, Morita asked me what I was going to do
I was scared, too
I saw it at first, but ignored it
I'd like to hear a clip of that moment, please
Talking about the future of comedy
With Mayumiko Ueno
Selina and
Tara-chan
Oswald is going well these days, isn't he?
Oswald?
Hatanaka-san is the main duo, right?
I've only seen you on TV.I've only seen Hatanaka on TV.
But Miki is the weakest.
Miki was the weakest.
And Mikawa-san tightened it up for me.
No, really.
I was scared.
But before that, I was a little excited.
I thought, "He's eating the story.
I was excited that I was eating the story.
I was excited.
So it's not a challenge, but...
I mean, I don't know you guys well enough to know what you're doing.
And then you showed me three impersonations that had nothing to do with each other.
It's a little bit...
It's hard to watch.
It's a little hard to watch.
And Mr. Oswald is a little bit...
There were a lot of things he wanted to do with them.
It's too serious.
Too serious.
You did it, too, didn't you, Mr. Sakamoto?
Yes, I did.
I was so scared.
First place.
Ten seconds.
I hate it.
I don't like it. I don't like it.
For those of you who haven't seen it.
For those who haven't seen it.
Mr. Sakamoto, please.Mr. Sakamoto, I'll leave you to it.
Eh?
Masaharu Fukuyama when he saw a boring VTR.
He's killing again.
LOL!
You look a little like him.
I've never done it before.
I haven't.
Second one-man live project presentation contest!
Here it is, the second one-man live concert to be held on August 11!
We're going to ask everyone to come up with ideas for the project corner to be held there.
But if you're OK with this and we decide to go with it, we'll actually do it, right?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, wow.
This is important.
Before that...
I heard that some people like the tense atmosphere when Kohyeon comes out.
I see.
Then, I'd like to invite Kohyun to join us today.
Here he comes!
He's here!
Wonderful!
Brother Kohyun, this is Mr. Ueda, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for the chair.
What did you think of Ueda's impersonation of Fujiko All Night?
I got a thrill out of it.
That's it.
No, no, no, that's it!
So I guess I'll let Ueda-san be the judge.So I'll let Ueda-san be the judge.
Yes, please do.
Let's go.
We'll have a quiz to see how well you know the members, and we'll also have a quiz for those who may be coming to the second one-man show for the first time.
We'll have a quiz about the members, for example, what girls like.
And also, I think the members like Disney, and maybe one of them will answer "Disney".
If all the respondents answered "ramen", it would be a success.
Oh, how about this, Mr. Uida?
This isn't really a quiz, is it?
Well, it's something we all agree on, so...
Unanimity isn't as important as the system we're using.
You're talking about taking the first one or the second one, right?
Well, yeah.
I see.
There's not much going on, is there?
That's right.
That's why, as we're talking about it now, the only things that come up are ramen and Disney.
It's a bit limited as a project.
Yes.
If I simulate a project and I think it won't expand that much, I won't do the homework.
Let's move on.
Let's go next time.
Okay, Hirita.
Yes, sir.
The second of RAFRAF
Oh, what's this?
The second of RAFRAF started this year.
show raceShow Race
I think the theme of the show race was to give veterans another chance.
This is something that we have been doing for a long time.
"Oh, I wish I had added this part..." or "If there was a second time, I would like to say this.
If there is a second chance, I would like to say something like this.
For example, in the case of daily performances, we would say that something happened and it was interesting.
For example, when Sakiguma-san appeared at the one-man show, the hair and makeup artist couldn't bear to look at him, so she arranged his hair.
When he told me that the hair and makeup artist who couldn't stand to see Sakiguma's appearance at his one-man live had done it for him...
I said in a whispered voice, "I can see that you've gotten a new look.
That was pretty harsh.
I'm sorry about that.
The blurriness is in there.
No, I didn't hear you.
I hear it now.
What about it?
Does that mean it's already there? Something I'd like to rephrase.
Yes, there's something I want to rephrase.
What did you say?
Well...
Oh, it's true, Sakiguma's cute sleeping habit makes everyone melt in love with him.
Well, well, well...
How do you like it, Mr. Ueda?
Yes, I do.
Well, it's good to be an idol, isn't it?
You made me do it!
White.
The concept is not bad.
But that's not what "The Second" is about, is it?
It's a project that's in line with The Second, but what we're doing isn't The Second.
Maybe it's a little slow to get across.Maybe it's a little slow to get through.
I see.
So why didn't you just ask the fans once the song was over?
That's the real second.
The one where you ask the audience.
Okay, then, Takanashi.
Takanashi.
I've come up with a plan to make everyone's requests come true, and I've made it into Meko Time.
The first one requires a little preparation.
But I've heard from many fans that they'd like us to do something like this even if it's not a live performance.
I've been getting a lot of requests from fans to do something like this even if it's not a live performance.
So I divided the 15 minutes into 333 parts.
For example, let's say you, Ryouka, Miku and Miri do a 3-minute skit.
For example, Ryouka, Miku, and Miri could do a 3-minute skit.
Anyway, we listen to a lot of requests from fans and make them come true in 15 minutes.
And then we will make them come true in the 15 minutes.
I hope we can get some laughs.
For example, Equal Love has a "kameko time" in their live performances.
It's called "kameko time" during the live performance.
Fans take pictures of their idols and post them on social networking sites.
Fans take pictures of their idols and post them on SNS, and it's a big hit.
This summer, Ruff Ruff's goal is to increase the number of fans.
Even though it's a project for the inner circle of one-on-one fans, it's still a great opportunity for them to get to know each other.
I'm going to let people take whatever pictures they want for the next 15 minutes.
and spread the word about it.
I'm hoping to get some new fans.
Wow, isn't that really strong?
You seem to have put a lot of thought into it.
What do you think?
Well, I think that recruiting from fans is a good idea.Well, I think it's a little too obvious that you're recruiting from the fans.
I think it's a little too obvious.
It's a little too vague.
It's easy to make excuses.
No, no, no. Excuses are not excuses.
No, it's not an excuse.
This is not an excuse.
Because a fan told you to.
Don't compromise on that.
I'll do my best to say what I'm told.
Well, I guess I can say that now.
Up there.
That's harsh.
How do you feel about this, Mr. Sagawa?
No, no, I think it's a well-done plan.
You should definitely have something like Cameco Time.
Uh, yes, yes, yes.
If you only offer what the fans want to see at the top.
There will be less betrayal.
Now, maybe some of the fan requests are fulfilled, but
But I think it's better to come up with something interesting that betrays the fans
I think it's better to have a surprise.
I mean, it's better to have surprises.
It's better to have a surprise.
I'll go over it a little more.
Come on.
This is a conference room.
Let's have them all come out at once.
Let's do it!
Okay.
What's the opening of the audition?What is the opening of an audition look back?
Well, it's been a year since the audition.
So, I'd like to have Hibino Saito alone at the beginning.
And then we'll talk about the audition process.
And then we'll sing a little bit of praise.
I thought that might make them cry at the beginning.
(Laughs)
So you're going to do a little bit of a sound play.
Yeah, like a skit.
Like the director's idea.
Sounds good.
What do you mean, "convey the individual charms of Nagamatsu"?
This is similar to what Yuu just said.
I'm going to do what we want to do.
That's exactly what I and Fu-chan want to do.
It's fine if we do a duet or something like that.
I think that when people come to the show
I thought that if they came to the show, they would get to know more about the charms of our music.
That's why I've put it out there.
I mean to let people know about each of you, right?
The important part.
And Saito's too.
That's what I meant.
I really wanted to do this.
When I heard it was going to be 15 minutes.
I thought it was a comedy.
And I recently...
You thought it was a 15-minute skit?
I've been doing this little race recently.I've recently been asked to participate in this small race and I've been working hard on my comedy side as well.
I've been working hard in the field of comedy
I would like to improve my writing skills and
I also
I want to raise my level.
I'm like a leader.
I have a lot of contact with the members.
I want to write a comedy that brings out the charm of each member.
Like Nagamatsu said in the skit.
Nagamatsu said in the skit.
I'd like to have him do a lot of different things
We could have them do various things.
This girl is also looking for clothes.
That kind of thing.
Someone could write that kind of thing.
Or someone could create a character like that.
That's a lot of work.
So you're going to write the guess work?
I'd like to write it.
That's amazing.
15 minutes is the length of Bananaman.
Like 033.
It's a solo show.
I'm submitting it to Sakuma.
It's a lot of work, Sakuma-san.
It's a lot of work for the original.
But this looks good, doesn't it?
It's a lot of people.
You mean we can include everyone's good qualities?
I thought it would bring out a new side of me.I thought I could bring out a new side of me.
I'm looking forward to it.
Is that it?
It's like a foreshadowing of what's to come.
You're looking at it too much as a stand-alone.
You're looking at it alone.
A master's alone?
I don't think that's going to happen.
Ramen complete!
Hayashi
Wave your towel to the new song
You just thought of a new song.
15 minutes
Wrong.
You wave your towel.
Yes, sir.
Where's Sasaki?
I put out a cheerleading project
I've come up with a new project called "Cheer Cheer".
Our new costumes...
"Cheerleading cheerleaders" and "Cheerleading cheerleaders".
And our song
to cheer people up.
and songs that encourage people.
I thought there are many lyrics in our songs
I brought pom-poms and other things
with pom-poms and stuff.
I thought of a cheerleader-like choreography
I thought it would be so cute if they performed it
It would be so cute and
And if Natsume simplyNatsume simply
I couldn't get into it.
I've never skied.
I'm sure you'll get in.
Say "Sky.
I'll rewrite it.
I've never done that before.
Have you?
Yes, I have.
I'm a great MC.
Great MC.
Have you ever done that?
I'll write it down.
We've all been asked to write it down.
I think I can do it.
I think it's a good one.
None of them are bad.
The one with Hibino and the others can be done without a live performance.
Well, you're right.
It's only because it's live, isn't it?
If that's the case...
I'd like to see the one with Takanashi's camera and the one with
And Nagamatsu's.
Saito's camera.
Wouldn't you like to see it for a moment?
I'd love to see that.
Let's have him write a script for now.
Write it for now.
We can do it another time.
Yes, you're right.
I'll make some corrections.I'll still make some corrections.
I'll make some corrections, right?
Let's work together, Mr. Ueda.
I'll be tough.
Is that harsh?
No, you're serious.
I'm serious.
Well then.
I'll do the same.
Well, it's decided.
You think you can do it? You think you can do it?
Well, I've only written pin stories.
No, it's rare that I've written a pin story.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Akane-san, Manamin, Sakuma-san said so...
I'll do a double attack.
Manamin, umm...
First, take the candy.
That's right.
Yui, too.
That's amazing.
You've thought of everything.
No, I don't.
It was fine.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'd love to do Kamiko time.
I'm definitely looking forward to seeing all the idols.
I'm definitely looking forward to it.
Peelie, go over to the edge and wipe your towel a little bit.Peelie, a little towel wipe at the end.
Just a little wipe.
The people waving around are Mie-chan's fans.
Oh no!
Watch YouTube, okay?
Yes, sir.
Amazing!
Here we go again.
Yugo Takahashi's second expedition into hot and spicy food!
Yay!
Hey...
Cute!
There's a cute girl.
Se-no
Oh, oh, oh,
Ah, ah,
Uh-oh,
Scary, scary.
Thank you for watching until the end.
This time, it's a cat version.
Meow, meow, meow, meow.
Meow, meow, meow, meow, meow.
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow.
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meowMeow Meow Meow Meow
Meow Meow Meow Meow Meow
Meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow meow
Meow meow meow meow meow
Meow.
Se-no, meow!